[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":43408,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":69709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":6980,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":76690,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10485,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":87176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":4766,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":91943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":17025,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":108969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2193,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":111163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your re sult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":12555,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":123720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1491,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":125211,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4796,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":130007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2  because  1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":131270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":134697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1302,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":136000,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the f irst num ber, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3523,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":139524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1219,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":140744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":145226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1261,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":146488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5594,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":152083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1475,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":153559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":158007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1053,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":159060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you  subtract  6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4890,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":163951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":164934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":15976,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":180912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":21275,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":202188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":14679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":216868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2049,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":218919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4526,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":223445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1699,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":225144,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inv erse of  3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3654,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":228798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1039,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":229837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2529,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":232366,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1547,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":233913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6629,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":240542,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":243711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":15621,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":259333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><b r /> How ever, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":21900,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":281234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":289058,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1708,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":290766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10- 0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":294474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":4496,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":298971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub >6</sub> ? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4451,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":303422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1281,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":304704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3268,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":307973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1752,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":309726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions  as accu rately as possible.","rt":18988,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":328715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":12149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":340866,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":5002,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":345868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":16749,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":362618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":366434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":371946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":378221,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["2","3"],"rt":6048,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":384270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8 because 8 + 1 = 9","response_history":["8 because i","8 because 8 + 1 +","8 because 8 + 1 = o","8 because 8 + 1 = 9"],"rt":34141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":418411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5 because 4+ 5 = 9","response_history":["5 because 4+ 5 = 0","5 because 4+ 5 = 9"],"rt":29660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":448071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because you can add it 9","response_history":["0 because you can add it 0","0 because you can add it 9"],"rt":21295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":469367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6193,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":475562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":5480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":481043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":3182,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":484226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 because 3 + 6 - 9","response_history":["6 because 3 + 6 - 9"],"rt":19787,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":504014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"2 yes because it can equal 9","response_history":["2 yes because it can equal 0","2 yes because it can equal 0","2 yes because it can equal 9"],"rt":19107,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":523121,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because all can equal 9","response_history":["yes because all can equal 9"],"rt":16702,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":539824,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no only 4 can equal 9","response_history":["no only 4 can equal 9"],"rt":14231,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":554055,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because only 3 can equal 9","response_history":["no becua","no becu","no because only 3 can equal 9"],"rt":14400,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":568455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":12614,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":581070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":8815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":589886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"W hat is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I dont know","response_history":["I dont know"],"rt":16787,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":606675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"theres a pattern because all elements can make it","response_history":["theres a pattern because all elements can make it"],"rt":22958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":629633,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n </sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":9030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":638664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6613,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":645278,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":651799,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"true I dont know you lost me","response_history":["true I dont know you lost me"],"rt":13801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":665600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9054,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":674656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</ sub>, is  x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"sometimes because not all numbers are a generator","response_history":["sometimes because not all numbers are a generator"],"rt":23822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":698478,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":702742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background . Please  press Continue to continue.","rt":2225,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":704967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"50","response_history":["50"],"rt":4146,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":709114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":713062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math  class y ou've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"basic math","response_history":["basic math"],"rt":8411,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":721474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":727155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"mu lti","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3532,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":730687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":735228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":10890,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":746119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":5802,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":751923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2748,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":754672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":6024,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":760697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":4301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":764999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":765102,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]